Guide to the Hartwell Family Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Personal Items and Memorabilia, Series IV
  - Photographs
    - re: ABH (Box 16, Folder 50)
    - re: AFU-LHU (Box 16, Folder 51)
    - re: LHU-CWNH (Box 16, Folder 52)
    - re: Chinese People (Box 16, Folder 53-58)
    - re: Chinese People (Box 22, Folder 7-10)
    - re: Chinese Scenes (Box 16, Folder 59-63)
    - re: Chinese Scenes (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - re: Family (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - re: Friends and Missionaries (Box 16, Folder 64-67)
    - re: Friends and Missionaries (Box 23, Folder 13-14)
    - re: Process of Making Thatched Roof (Box 16, Folder 68)
    - re: Picture Post Cards (Box 16, Folder 69)
    - re: Large Groups (Box 16, Folder 70)
    - re: First Christian College in China; First School for the Deaf in China;Temple Hill - Northern Presbyterian Mission, c. 1890; c. 1900; Before 1890 (Box 16, Folder 71)
    - re: Burning of the Chapei district of Shanghai by Japanese - afternoon and evening, 1937 (Box 17, Folder 72)
    - re: Harry Luce in group with son, Henry Luce (Box 17, Folder 73)
    - re: Mounted Pictures (Chinese Scenes) (Box 17, Folder 74)
    - re: Large Groups (Box 17, Folder 75)
    - re: from album of Shaohing (Box 17, Folder 76)
    - Photograph album (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Photograph albums (AFU-Shaohing, China) (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Photograph - group, probably missionaries, taken in front of a building identified as "State Capitol in Boston", ca. 1879 (Box 23, Folder OV1)